? 超級碗 ?
♪ Oh, Super Bowl ♪
? 精彩比賽 比賽精彩 萬眾期待 ?
♪ The plays, the plays, they're calling ♪
? 從一端到另一端 ?
♪ From end to end ♪
? 還有啊 ?
♪ And -- ♪
發生什么事了
What happened?
要我撥打9和1還再加一個1嗎
Do I call the nine and the one and the other one?
為什么我的冰箱都是與橄欖球無關的食物
Why is my fridge filled with non-football-related foods
今天可是有超級碗大賽的星期天
on Super Bowl Sunday?
都沒地方放我的杰瑞·賴斯布丁了
There's no room for my Jerry Rice pudding.
今天是海莉的迎嬰派對
Haley's baby shower is today.
我大概一個月前就跟你說過了
I cleared it with you, like, a month ago.
你就不能把比賽錄下來嗎
Can't you just record the game?
然后呢 明早再看嗎
And what? Watch it tomorrow morning?
為什么橄欖球比賽和迎嬰派對
Look. There's no reason a football game and a baby shower
就不能同處一個屋檐下呢
can't co-exist under the same roof.
你們應該也不會打擾到我
Maybe you won't get in my way.
迎嬰派對挺平淡的
Baby showers are pretty tame.
迎嬰派對啊啊的朋友們 你們好哇
Who's ready for a baby show-ahhh?!
我在為迎嬰派對啊啊做白色俄羅斯人
I'm making White Russians for the baby show-ahhh.
一點液體勇氣能讓"壞壞游戲"更好玩
A little liquid courage makes all the naughty games better.
我覺得你把迎嬰派對和婚前派對搞混了
I think you're mixing up baby shower with bridal shower.
我的婚前派對就是在我懷孕的時候舉行的
Well, my bridal shower did take place when I was pregnant.
"警察"[舞男]都來了
The cops even showed up.
當然了 他們不是真警察
Of course, they weren't real cops.
其中一個還用屁股蹭我的肚子
One of them rubbed his butt against my belly.
別跟海莉說
Don't tell Haley.
不如"別跟艾麗克斯說"
Or how about, "Don't tell Alex"?
超級碗投注站來啦
Super Bowl squares here!
快給你的超級碗下注吧
Get your Super Bowl squares!
別 別又來一次
No. Not this again.
其實我們做了一點改良
Uh, actually, we've made some refinements.
去年的價格有點太高了
Last year, the price was a little high.
前年又太低了
The year before, too low.
所以今年 我們確定了一個完美的數額
So this year, we've landed on the perfect number.
每注3.75美元
$3.75 per square.
我會跟去年一樣
I'll do what I did last year.
-給我11注 -行啊 容易得很
- Give me 11 squares. - Okay. Easy enough.
不要在迎嬰派對這邊搞什么超級碗的算術
No. No Super Bowl math on the baby shower side.
到那邊去
Go over there.
我告訴你 你真的看起來很棒
I'm telling you, you look cute.
你知道什么不棒嗎 對我撒謊
You know what's not cute? Lying to me.
孩子出生后 脾氣就會改了吧
This gets better once they come out, right?
-怎么了 -我的上一條牛仔褲穿不上了
- What happened? - Well, my last pair of jeans exploded,
我不能穿裙子 因為我的大腿長毛了
I can't wear skirts because my thighs are growing hair
剃都剃不及
faster than I can shave it,
所以我只能穿著滑雪褲來參加自己的迎嬰派對
so I'm wearing ski pants to my own baby shower.
我告訴你 沒人會注意到的
I'm telling you, no one's even gonna notice.
那是什么聲音 聽起來好像
What's that sound? It's like
進取號星艦艙門開啟的聲音
when the doors on the starship Enterprise open.
你們想給超級碗下注嗎
Hey, you guys want to buy a Super Bowl square?
每注只要3.75美元噢
Only $3.75.
酷 我能要三注嗎
Cool. Can I take three squares?
是啊 我今天得有點好事
Yeah, I need something good today, too.
我們合買五注
We'll split five squares.
你有零錢嗎
Uh...do you have quarters?
上次我被閃電打中之后
Oh, I don't carry change
我就不隨身帶著零錢了
since the last time I got struck by lightning.
你好 菲利普
Hello, Phillip.
你好 曼尼爾
Hello, Manuel.
違背我明智的判斷力
Against my better judgment,
我在新電影里為菲爾寫了一段戲
I wrote a part for Phil in my new movie.
后來事態有些劍拔弩張 兩人間唇槍舌劍
Things got heated, words were exchanged,
這點還挺令人意外 嘴這么利說臺詞卻這么愚鈍
which is surprising, considering he had a mouthful of scenery.
演員啊
Actors.
編劇啊 他們自視甚高
Writers. They think they're so great.
"我寫的詞真是字字珠璣"
"Oh, my words are so precious."
學著傾聽一下吧
Try listening for once.
那樣你或許會知道人究竟是怎么說話的
Maybe you'll learn how humans actually talk.
等等 是"說"還是"曰"來著
Wait, is it -- is it "talk" or "speak"?
想起來了
Oh, that's right.
根本沒人在意
No one cares!
大家好 我來看超級碗大賽啦
Hello, hello. I'm here for the Super Bowl.
-我是來參加迎嬰派對的 -行 好
- And I am here for the baby shower. - Okay, yep.
我好像是來受什么刑的
I'm here for some sort of punishment, I think.
莉莉和她朋友克里斯蒂娜大吵一架
Hmm. Lily and her friend, Christina, got into a huge fight.
我希望我們能夠
And I was hoping we could
讓她們坐下來好好聊聊
have the girls sit down and talk it out.
但米奇爾說"不 克里斯蒂娜是錯的"
But Mitchell said "No, Christina's in the wrong."
很顯然 米奇爾言出法隨
And apparently, Mitchell's the law.
他確實是 莉莉 你真幸運有個這樣睿智的爸爸
He is. Lily, you're very lucky to have such a wise papa.
普里契特助理地檢是個英雄
Mm-hmm. Assistant District Attorney Pritchett is a hero.
所以這人現在覺得你酷斃了
Huh. So this one thinks you're cool now?
歌洛莉亞喜歡犯罪故事
Okay, Gloria loves crime stories,
特別是殺夫的女人那種
especially women who kill their husbands.
最近我起訴了貝艾爾市的黑寡婦
And I recently prosecuted the Bel Air Black Widow.
她每天都有來法庭
She came to court every single day.
我們認為被告有罪
We find the defendant guilty.
太好了
Yes! Whoop, whoop!
律師 這事兒沒完
Hey, Counselor. This isn't over.
女士 你就像高中的我一樣
Lady, you're like me in high school,
因為你17年內都別想出來[出柜]
cause you ain't gonna be coming out for 17 years!
虐了一個外焦內嫩
Boom goes the dynamite!
小卡 來一碗我的知名辣椒醬
Cam, have a bowl of my famous chili.
我都不知道你做了這個
I didn't know you made chili.
我對杰該死的辣椒醬熟得很
I know all about Jay's damn chili.
就在去年的同一天我們還聊過
We talked about it last year on this very day.
我們還做了約定
Promises were made.
明年 我會給你買一把你自己的橄欖球椅
Next year, I'm getting you your own football chair
你來幫忙我做我的知名辣椒醬
and you're gonna help me make my famous chili.
凌晨五點
5: 00 a.M.
不見不散
Be there or be square.
我從未完全感受到杰的認同
You know, I never entirely felt Jay's approval,
所以這對我們來說是一大步
so this was a big step for us.
我每天都數著日子
I counted the days.
然后超級碗的前夕
Then Super Bowl Eve,
我去了 還買了最好的辣椒醬增稠劑
I went and I bought the finest chili thickeners --
玉米面粉還有土豆面粉
corn flour and potato flour.
我在黎明前一小時出現
And I showed up an hour before dawn.
為了不嚇到歌洛莉亞 我給杰打了電話
I called Jay's cell as to not startle Gloria.
什么事啊
Hey, what's up?
他完全沒意識到我為什么打給他
He had no idea why I was calling.
承諾很明顯對他來說一點都不重要
Clearly promises made didn't mean as much to him.
但是我不能讓他知道
But I couldn't let him know that.
杰 是你嗎
Oh, uh, Jay, is th-- is that you?
我肯定是沒鎖屏按到了
I-I must -- I must've butt-dialed you.
不然我為什么要在一個這么平常的
Why else would I be calling you so early...
周日早晨給你打電話呢
...on a regular Sunday morning?
抱歉
Sorry.
我覺得自己被負心漢拋棄了
I felt like a jilted lover
站在他的門廊前 手里拿著美麗的面粉[音同鮮花]
standing on his porch, holding those beautiful flours.
你不能躲在這一整天
You can't hide in here all day.
我覺得你現在的樣子最性感
To me, you've never been hotter,
而我可是看過比你穿比基尼搭便車時的樣子呢
and I've seen you hitchhike in a bikini.
你在這啊
There you are.
很遺憾你今天過得不太好
I'm sorry you're having a bad day, uh...
不過我覺得應該告訴你 我邀請了丹妮爾
but I thought you should know, I invited Danielle.
丹妮爾 她太討人厭了
Danielle? Ugh, she's so annoying.
她說的每句話聽著都像個問句咩
Everything she says sounds like a question?
但其實不是咩
But it's not?
是啊 但是她正處在
Yeah, but she's in her, like,
第好多個月的孕期
thousandth month of pregnancy.
天啊
Oh, my God.
那我就不是這里最丑的孕婦了
That means I won't be the grossest preggo here.
太愛你了
Bless you.
謝謝
Thanks.
謝謝你今天邀請我過來
And thanks for inviting me today.
當然了 你是孩子的爸爸
Of course. You're the baby's father.
是 但是這是家庭聚會
Yeah, but it's a family thing,
而我一直覺得不能融入你們
and I don't always feel like I belong.
有的時候他們看我就像
Sometimes they look at me like
俗話中的"掃興使[屎]者"一樣
the proverbial bird in the punch bowl.
難得只錯一個字
Almost.
三乘
Uh, three times...
不好意思 不過不管你怎么看
I'm sorry, but every way you look at it,
迪蘭的錢數不對[不夠格]
Dylan comes up short.
海莉完全就被騙了
And Haley's totally getting rooked.
好吧 這有點意思
Oh! Okay, well, that's interesting.
他們在郡監獄里找不到黑寡婦了
Um, they lost track of the Black Widow at the county jail.
-她越獄了 -是啊
- She escaped? - Mm-hmm.
-你害怕嗎 -開什么玩笑
- Are you scared? - What?!
就是嘛
Exactly!
應該害怕的是她
She should be scared of you.
如果她夠聰明 就應該逃得遠遠的
If she's smart, that young lady will run and keep running.
這里面放了什么調料
What spice is in here?
是茴香嗎
Is it -- Is that dill?
里面放茴香[迪蘭在這]干什么
Why the hell is dill in here?
真是災難啊
It's a -- It's a catastrophe.
我重新利用一下這里的一點頭發
So, I'm just gonna repurpose some of this hair
蓋住禿處和青春痘
to cover the bald spot and zits --
-還有青春痘 -全"痘"會看起來美美的
- Zits?! - And "Zits" Gonna look amazing.
完成啦
Ta da!
-成了嗎 -是啊
- Ta da?! - Yeah.
我真有膽梳這種遮禿發型
I have a huge gut and a comb-over.
看上去像個離了婚的牙醫
I look like a divorced dentist.
丹妮爾
Oh, Danielle!
你看起來真不錯 為什么
You look so good. Why?
是懷孕的魔力咩 話題"老天保佑"
It's the magic of pregnancy? #Blessed?
什么情況
What the hell?!
艾麗克斯說我可以早點過來
Alex said it was okay if I came early?
海莉 我真為你高興
Haley, I'm so happy for you?
我需要迪蘭 迪蘭呢
I need Dylan. Where is Dylan?
迪蘭去哪了
Where's Dylan?
海莉找不到他的
Haley's not gonna find Dylan.
他走了
He's gone,
你們每個人都有錯
and it's everybody's fault!
怎么都哭喪著個臉
What is up with all the funeral faces?
來嗨呀 大伙 這可是
Come on, people, this is supposed to be
-迎嬰派對啊啊 -別再這么稱呼了
- a baby show-ahhh. - Don't say "Show-ahhh".
沒人覺得好
Nobody wants it.
好吧 所以迪蘭誤會了我們
Okay. So, Dylan misunderstood
說的一些話 傷了感情走了
a bunch of the things he heard us say, got upset, and ran off.
我們就別假裝是什么誤會
Let's not pretend this was some mistake
或者迪蘭太敏感了
or Dylan being oversensitive.
我們都做了很多讓他覺得
We've all given him plenty of reasons
在這個家里不受歡迎的事
to feel unwelcome in this family.
有的人確實很無情
And some of us do have a meanness.
我就這么說吧 毫無人性的殘酷
I'll leave it at that. A monstrous cruelty.
簡而言之 就是虐待狂
Enough said. Sadistic.
我們家就挺冷靜的
My family is really chill?
就不該讓你來
You were a mistake.
好了 盧克拖住了海莉
Okay, Haley's being occupied by Luke,
所以我們還有些時間
so we have some time.
我們得找到迪蘭
We just have to find Dylan
不能讓海莉知道他跑掉了
without letting Haley know he's run away.
不過這聽著是迎嬰派對的問題
That kind of sounds like a shower problem, though.
我不是很理解為什么要
I don't know how fair it is to bring in
把看超級碗的人攪和進來
the Super Bowl folk into this.
我的姐姐給了我這個機會為她辦迎嬰派對
My big sister gave me the honor of hosting her shower,
我就要辦得漂漂亮亮
and it's gonna be great.
所以 唯一可能知道
So, the one person
迪蘭去了哪里的人 也就是海莉
who might know where Dylan went, Haley,
卻不能知道他不見了
is the one person who can't know he's missing.
這就是我所稱的戲劇性的一幕
That's what I call a dramatic situation.
你不是應該趁勢大導特導一下這部戲嗎
Shouldn't you be directing the life out of it?
喬 迪蘭不高興的時候喜歡去哪
Joe, where does Dylan like to go when he's depressed?
艾麗克斯 他喜歡迪蘭沒錯 但也沒有
Alex, he likes him, but it's not like --
公園 寵物店 吉他店
Park, pet store, guitar shop.
怎么 我關注他的照片分享網了
What? I follow his Instagram.
他有雙發現美的眼睛
He finds beauty in the mundane.
好 我們分頭找迪蘭
Okay. We'll search for Dylan in teams.
-米奇 歌洛莉亞 找公園 -太好了
- Mitch, Gloria -- park. - Score.
吉他店 小卡 杰
Guitar store -- Cam, Jay.
寵物店 菲爾 曼尼 走吧
And the pet store -- Phil, Manny, go.
-我能換個... -你想把漂亮臉蛋
- Actually, could I trade? - Your pretty face
換成被打得腫起來的臉嗎 來試試看啊
for one that's been freshly whooped? Try me!
我可不可以...
Would it be possible if I could --
-快走 -算了 到店里再去洗手間好了
- Move! - Ah, they'll have a bathroom at the store.
他沒卡在旋轉滑梯里
He's not stuck in the tube slide.
去兒童節目主持人去世時
Ah, it was too much to hope he'd be
他躲起來的地方找他的確有點勉強
where we found him when Mister Rogers died.
"你惹錯老娘了 我來找你了"
"You messed with the wrong girl. I'm coming for you."
這人是誰
Who is this?
貝爾艾爾區號
That's Bel Air.
黑寡婦越獄后就開始威脅你了
The Black Widow is out and already threatening you?
太好了
This is good.
你可以抓住她 再做一次英雄
You get to catch her and be a hero again.
或許我該給黑寡婦發條信息
You know, maybe I should-I should send the Black Widow
告訴她"只是公事公辦 別記仇"
a-a "no hard feelings" text.
-不 -不
- No. - No?
你在庭上說的都是對的
What you said in court was right.
那個禽獸不值得姑息
That animal deserved no mercy.
她活該被關在籠子里
She deserves a cage.
我說了些狠話 她也說了些狠話
Well, you know, I said some things, she said some things.
這 等等
It's -- Wait, um...
"我不怕 放馬過來"
"I am not afraid. Bring it on."
好吧
I -- Oh, okay.
所有惡霸都一樣
All bullies are the same.
他們裝出一副狠相
They act like they're tough,
可當你朝他們鼻子來一拳 他們就縮了
but when you punch 'em in the nose, they back down.
是啊
Yeah.
"我知道你住哪 你死定了"
"I know where you live. You're dead."
這種回復很罕見
That response is rare.
他在這
There he is.
迪蘭
Dylan.
Hey, Dylan!
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
這是我第三次犯完全一樣的錯誤了
That's the third time I've made that exact same mistake.
讓我開始質疑越戰時的一些約會對象
Makes me wonder about some of my dates in 'Nam.
他不在這 我們走
Well, he ain't here. Let's go.
我知名的辣椒醬從凌晨五點就在燉了
My famous chili has been simmering since 5:00 a.m.
說來有趣
Y-you know, it is funny
你一直說你的辣椒醬"知名"
that you keep calling your chili "famous"
可我覺得有點
when I find it a little...
吃過就忘
forgettable.
小卡 我是個成功的男人
Cam, I'm a successful man.
業界巨頭
Captain of industry,
跟嘉寶姐妹之一親熱過
made out with a Gabor sister,
假如我能在董事會再拉點票
and if I can swing a few more board votes,
我們在俄亥俄州的
we break ground on
普里切特衣櫥科學院就能破土動工
the Pritchett School of Closet Science at Ohio State.
我真不在乎你怎么看我的辣椒醬
Not really sweating your take on my chili.
他傷我至深
He'd hurt me deeply.
我一直提辣椒醬是因為
I kept mentioning chili 'cause, you know,
我想刺激一下他的記憶
I was trying to jog his memory,
因為我們本該一起做的
'cause we were supposed to make it together.
我一輩子都想找個專門一起看超級碗的伙伴
I've waited my whole life for a special Super Bowl buddy,
能明白這不只是一場球賽的人
someone who understands it isn't just a game.
這是場15小時 4頓飯
It's a 15-hour, 4-meal,
2件上衣 1次打盹的體驗
2-shirt, 1-nap experience,
我以為小卡會是那個伙伴
and I thought Cam could be that buddy.
然后我開始擔心
Then I started worrying
小卡或許忘了我們一年前的約定
Cam might forget a date we set a year ago.
他還記得
He remembered.
他還記得 斯黛拉
He remembered, Stella!
冷靜點
Be cool.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
沒鎖屏按到了
Oh, butt-dial.
不 我明白
No, I see.
是啊 沒事
Yeah, take it easy.
鼻子印 男性 高個子
Nose print, man's -- face high,
視線直對兔寶寶
direct eye-line to baby bunnies.
迪蘭來過這
Dylan was here.
這家伙就要做家長了
This guy's about to have a kid.
-什么樣的成年男性 -它們要醒了
- What kind of adult male -- - They're waking up.
它們要醒了
They're waking up.
他不在這
Hey, look, he's not here.
我們回派對上去吧
Let's just get back to the parties.
我得先去一趟街對面的自助洗衣店
Ooh, I got to stop at that laundromat across the street.
一下就好 我的投注站需要零錢
It'll take a second. I just need change for my squares.
有趣 你感興趣的事情你就這么上心
Funny. You're so focused when it's your passion project.
你知道嗎 曼尼
Y-you know what, Manny?
你說得對
You're right.
那整件事都是我不好
That whole thing was my bad.
謝了 菲爾
Thanks, Phil.
我把兩邊門都打開好讓你這大頭癥進得去
Let me get both these doors so you and your ego can fit inside.
我不知道你怎么能生我的氣
I don't know how you can get mad at me
是你先發了那段丟人的視頻
after posting that humiliating video.
什么視頻
What video?
別裝傻
Don't play dumb.
-俺冷 -停
- Me cold. - Cut!
"我好冷"
"I'm so cold."
不是"俺冷" 不是"我不是不冷"
Not "Me cold." Not "I'm not not cold."
不是"冰 冰 寶貝"[歌詞]
Not "Ice, ice baby."
沒有正常人會那么說話
No humans say those things!
你要人記住的東西太多了
It is so difficult to build a performance
想好好表演太難了
with a constant barrage of notes!
就一點 別改臺詞
Note! Say the line!
就三個字
Three words!
你知道我想聽哪幾個字嗎
You know what three words I'd like to hear?
"死得好 菲爾"
"Nice death, Phil!"
我只是想幫你
I'm just trying to help you,
你耍什么大牌
you diva !
而你自己高潮個沒完
And you keep yourself.
蠢貨 蠢貨 蠢貨 蠢貨
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
難以置信
Unbelievable!
蠢貨 蠢貨 蠢貨 蠢貨 蠢貨
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
幸好影片在我真正發飆前就結束了
Fortunately, it cut off right before I really lost it.
曼尼 怎么會是我發的呢
Manny, why would I post a video
視頻里說我是"糟糕的演員"
calling myself a "terrible actor"?
很可能是我的剪輯師發的
Could've been my editor.
在一次關于創作很強烈的爭執中
During a particularly intense creative discussion,
我或許在他女友面前扇了他嘴巴
I may have slapped him in front of his girlfriend.
菲爾 我很抱歉
Phil, I'm sorry.
我認為我很鬧心的原因
I think the reason I got frustrated
只有一部分是因為你爛得氣人
is only partly due to your infuriating incompetence.
承認起來不難吧
Was that so hard?
別告訴別人 我申請了轉學
Between us, I've applied to transfer
去我可以主修會計或法律的學校
to somewhere I can major in accounting or law.
好糊口的專業
Something safe.
我開始質疑
I've started to question
自己是否有拍攝電影的才華
if I have any talent as a filmmaker.
我們來找出答案吧
Let's find out.
影片你帶在身上嗎
You got your film with you?
在我手機里
On my phone.
我們有最合適的測試觀眾
We have a perfect test audience.
嘗試一把
Take a chance. Let's, uh...
看看你有什么能耐
Let's see what you got.
好吧 我正好也帶了投影儀
Okay. I mean, I got my projector.
屏幕也有了
And a screen.
-好吧 我去準備 -太好了
- All right. I'll set it up. - Great.
與此同時 我變個魔術把場子弄熱
Meanwhile, I'll warm up the crowd with a magic trick.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
請大家把錢包放入這個枕頭套
I need everyone to put their wallets in this pillow case
然后面壁站著
and turn and face the wall.
都找遍了 沒人知道迪蘭在哪里
Well, that's it. No one knows where Dylan is.
他們最好趕緊找到他
They better.
她的朋友20分鐘后就會到
Her friends are gonna be here in 20 minutes --
就是那群人在畢業派對上
the same ones who at a graduation party
投票選她最有可能懷孕且沒男人
voted her most likely to be pregnant and alone.
就像我總說的那樣
Like I always say --
沒朋友好過有一群毒舌朋友
it's better to have no friends than mean friends.
這個嘛
Well...
迪蘭一向遇事就跑
Dylan's always been a runner.
天啊 你還記得他以前染金發嗎
God, you remember when he was a blond?
我叫他"瘋染夫人"
Ugh, I called him "Lady Dye-Job"
他就跑走了 我還得去找他...
and he ran off, and I had to track him down...
我知道迪蘭在哪了 我知道他在哪
I know where Dylan is. I know where he is!
迪蘭
Dylan.
迪蘭 開門 我是克萊爾
Hey, Dylan, open up. It's Claire.
我不想談 鄧菲太太
I -- I don't want to talk, Mrs. D.
我知道你很難過
Look, I realize you're upset.
但小卡 米奇 盧克 菲爾
But those things that Cam and Mitch
還有歌洛莉亞說的那些話
and Luke and Phil and Gloria said,
其實 都只是小誤會
they're -- they were just, uh, silly misunderstandings.
好吧
Okay.
可是你說的那些話呢
But what about what you said?
你知道我們得給家里所有柜子
You realize we're gonna have to baby-proof
裝上寶寶防護條吧
all the cabinets at home, right?
想象一下我們看著迪蘭
Think of how cute it'll be
努力想打開柜門 有多好笑
watching Dylan try to get into them.
我不該那么說
I shouldn't have said that,
我顯然也沒料到...
and I obviously didn't realize --
什么 我能聽懂那個笑話嗎
What? That I would get that joke?
太傷人了 鄧菲太太
The insult set it up, Mrs. D.
-"瘋染夫人"也會受傷的 -迪蘭
- "Lady Dye-Job" has feelings. - Oh, Dylan.
迪蘭 別這樣 親愛的 派對快開始了
Dylan, come on. Honey, the party is starting --
求你了 我很抱歉
Please. I -- I'm sorry.
我走了
I'm leaving.
開門 我是岡薩雷斯先生
Open up. It's Mr. Gonzales,
泊車員
the parking attendant.
我又不是傻子 鄧菲太太
I'm not an idiot, Mrs. D.
我知道你去找了岡薩雷斯先生來
I know you just went to get Mr. Gonzales
想趁我開門給他時沖進來
so you could run in here when I open the door for him.
迪蘭
Hey. Hey, Dylan?
迪蘭 迪...
Dylan? Dyl--
我靠
Ohh, damn it!
能快點嗎 我想回去跟克里斯蒂娜道歉
Can we hurry? I want to get back so I can apologize to Christina.
別啊 莉莉 為什么冒受心傷的險
Oh, no. Lily, why risk your heart?
克里斯蒂娜只會傷害你
Christina will just hurt you.
我完全同意 莉莉
I couldn't agree more, Lily.
如果克里斯蒂娜不懂得欣賞你的體貼 幽默
If Christina doesn't appreciate your warmth, your humor,
還有你那些精彩的人生故事
your great stories,
她就不值得你那么在乎她
she's just not worth it.
也許等她老了 孤零零住在那棟大房子里時
Oh, maybe she'll regret taking you for granted
她就會后悔當初沒好好珍惜你
when she's old and alone in that big house
并且意識到擁有再多的錢 也無法溫暖她的心
and realizes all that money can't keep her warm.
什么情況
What is happening?
現在還在洗衣店放電影了
Movies in a laundromat now?
嬉皮士就不能讓事物保持原來的樣子嗎
Can't hipsters just let a thing be a thing?
我還有很多話想跟你說 阿列克謝
There is much I wish to say to you, Alexei,
不只是現在 還有未來很長時間
not just now, but for long time.
一次忽視 怎么就葬送了20年的友情呢
How could one slight cost 20 years friendship?
是19世紀俄國人的愚蠢驕傲嗎
Silly 19th century Russian pride?
我們為什么沒有勇氣抓住愛呢
Why we not have courage to take chance on love?
我等凡人都是愚者
Fools, us humans.
現在還不算太遲
It's not too late.
但我沒時間了
It is for me,
我最好最好的朋友
my great, great friend.
現在我去天上的大克里姆林宮了
I go now to grand Kremlin in the sky.
好冷啊[辣椒醬]
It's chilly.
辣椒醬
Chili.
他為什么要提起這個
Why did he have to mention that?
我們今早本該一起煮辣椒醬的 小卡
We were supposed to cook together this morning, Cam.
我一直等著你呢
I waited for you.
可我帶著面粉到你家門口了
But I was there on your front porch with flours.
你還記得帶增稠劑
You remembered the thickeners?
我當然記得 我以為你忘了
Of course I did. I thought you forgot.
我還做了件一模一樣的給你
I have an identical one for you!
杰 你不知道這對我來說多有意義
Oh, Jay, you don't know how much this means to me!
莉莉 你必須跟克里斯蒂娜道歉
Lily, you -- you have to apologize to Christina.
沒錯
That's right.
別像我跟小卡 瑟吉和阿列克謝那樣
Don't be like me and Cam and Sergei and Alexei.
-自尊心就是毒藥 -沒錯 敞開心扉
- Pride is poison! - Yes, open your heart!
讓自己勇敢去愛
Let yourself love!
杰
Jay...
所以沒人好奇菲爾姑父
So, nobody's wondering why Uncle Phil
為什么會出演洗衣店電影嗎
is starring in a laundromat movie?
不
N-No-o-o-o!
怎么樣
So?
稱不上
It's...
特別優秀
not very good.
我就知道 純屬浪費時間
I knew it. I wasted my time.
但比之前那部電影好多了
But it's much better than the last one,
而且有一幕特別打動我
and there was one moment when Count Ivanovich was --
就是伊萬諾維奇伯爵跟熊下象棋那幕
was playing chess with the bear that really moved me.
那段本來就是
Well, that was supposed to be
整部電影的悲情內核體現
the emotional gestalt of the piece.
你甚至能在背景音里聽到我在忍著哭
You can hear me stifle a sob in the cut
這是因為話筒收音員故意壞我電影
because my boom operator was undermining me.
你的劇組真的很有毒
You had an astonishingly toxic set.
聽我說 曼尼 如果我是你父親
Listen, Manny, if I was your dad,
我可能會讓你選靠譜的工作
I might tell you to play it safe with your career.
但以粉絲的角度
But as a fan,
我迫不及待想看到你未來的作品
I'm dying to see what you come up with next.
-真的嗎 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我從你這么點大的時候就在聽你編故事
I've been watching you make up stories since you were this big.
我想看到結局
I want to see how it ends.
不是這電影的結局
Not that.
我是想看到你會走向何方
I-I want to see how this ends.
謝謝你 菲爾
Thanks, Phil.
我也想再接再厲
I would like to keep trying,
或許拍一些不那么商業化的片子
maybe something not so commercial.
太好了
That's great.
但我覺得這大概是我悲劇演員的終點了
I do think it's the end of the road for me as a thespian, though.
這樣也好
Probably best.
我下一部電影有一個你這年紀的角色
Well, I did have a part in my next film for a guy your age,
但你得有傅滿洲那種胡須
but you'd have to grow a Fu Manchu moustache
還得在2周內漲18公斤
and gain 40 pounds in two weeks.
我周二就能準備好
I'll be ready Tuesday.
-香菜 -正確
- Cilantro. - Yes.
-紅洋蔥丁 -你真厲害
- Diced red onion? - You are good.
還沒猜完你可不許跑
Hey, don't run away with the rest of that.
這是什么離奇畫面
Ugh, what am I looking at?
米奇爾 過來展示一下什么是真正的爺們
Mitch, come here. Show them how to be a real man.
他收到別人的威脅黒函一整天了
He has been getting threatening texts all day
是個逃犯 但他眼皮都不眨一下
from a fugitive, and he hasn't even flinched.
他們就慶幸自己是美嬌男吧
Well, they're lucky they're pretty, right?
老爸 我能借用你的手機嗎
Daddy, can I borrow your phone?
我想跟克里斯蒂娜道歉
I want to apologize to Christina.
莉莉 不行 他的手機可能會成為
Lily, no. His phone might be evidence
-謀殺審判庭上的證物 -誰被殺
- in a murder trial. - Whose?
小寶貝 你都用你小爸的手機跟朋友發短信嗎
Sweetie, have you been using Daddy's phone to text your friend?
是啊 我說了一些很毒的話
Yeah, and I said some mean stuff.
她估計也沒少罵回來
She's probably been texting me back.
天啊 好吧 行
My God. Okay, okay.
"我現在就在你家外
"I'm -- I'm right outside your house.
一切到此結束"
This ends now."
"對了 你的發型真難看"
"P.S., your hair's ugly."
她吹牛逼呢 她才不在外面
It's a bluff. She's not out there.
但如果你想去確認的話就去吧
I mean, if you want to go check, check.
如果你能去看一眼的話
You know, us weaklings would feel so much better
我們小弱雞會安心許多 拜托了
if you would just take a quick look. Please.
身為一個法界人士與保護者
Well, as -- as lawman and protector,
這點小事不足... 不足掛齒
that is something that I -- I can do.
謝謝你了 迪蘭
Thank you for this, Dylan,
我很感謝你愿意原諒我
and I appreciate you forgiving me
之前說的那些蠢話
for the dumb thing I said earlier.
誰說我原諒你了
Who said I forgave you?
我為你包扎傷口
I'm only treating your injury
純粹是因為你正在我家做客
because you're a guest in my home.
我知道表面上看來 我一直沒接納你
I know it may seem that I haven't always accepted you,
但我剛認識你那會兒 你是個穿著皮夾克
but when I met you, you were an 18-year-old in a leather jacket
泡我15歲女兒的18歲男孩
dating my 15-year-old daughter.
我理解
I get it.
你也是想保護你女兒
You were trying to protect your daughter
不被我這種男人染指
from a guy like me,
但我已經有很久沒當"我這樣的男人"了
but I haven't been a guy like me for a long time.
彎曲[通融]一下
Bend for me.
很難啊 迪蘭
It's hard, Dylan.
我當了那么多年的護女狂魔...
I have been a mama bear for so long...
不是 是彎起手肘
No, your elbow.
好的
Okay.
只... 只是一切都發展太快
It's j-- It's all happening so fast.
但已經在發展了
But it is happening.
我馬上就要成為你孫兒的父親了
I'm about to be the father to your grandbabies.
伸出手吧
Reach out a little.
我是指用心
I meant emotionally.
我敢直面鏡子
I can look myself in the mirror
知道自己已經盡了最大努力
and know that I've tried my hardest
為我與你的關系付出
to make our relationship work.
你也能做到嗎
Can you do the same?
來吧
Go ahead.
來 我幫你開燈光
Here, let me give you some light.
錯了 不是這個色
Oops, uh, not that one.
的確
No.
一個家庭的成長有許多種方式
There are a lot of ways for a family to grow...
達陣得分
Touchdown!
找到你們不知道對方也喜歡的愛好
...finding interests you didn't know you shared...
別這樣 我有兩周時間呢
Come on, I've got two weeks!
先用瞇瞇眼看 你瞧
Blur your eyes. Look at this.
找到能一起踏上的冒險之旅
...finding new challenges to embark on together...
但這很廢功夫
But it takes a lot of work.
一個家庭最好的成長方法
The best way for families to grow
就是為它開枝散葉
is by adding to them.
這杯敬我們家庭最新的成員們
So this is to the newest members of our family.
我很期待多熟悉你們所有人
I look forward to getting to know all of you.
-我愛你們 -干杯
- Love you. - Cheers.
我... 我要凍死了
I'm fre... freezing.
卡
Cut.
這天氣還能再冷一點嗎
Could it be any colder?
錯了
No.
是戴毛帽的季節了吧
Fur hat weather, no?
還錯
No.
我好冷
I'm so cold.
開始
And action.
鳥 對吧
Bird, am I right?
你是不是耍我
You gotta be kidding me.